The Amanda Seale Show.
We are joined by our headliner of the week, Kimberly Renee.
And we are in the midst of a for the record.
What is a song that reminds you of your favorite place you've traveled?
I thought I did.
I did.
I don't prefer this artist, but I'm still going to say what reminded me.
Paris.
So I know people have given Paris such like a bad rap.
I know.
But I loved Paris so much.
I want to sit in a table and just, you know, have a little mocktail, you know, sex with somebody next to somebody handsome and be cozy.
You know, that's my vibe.
I had a moment where I had this man come into a space that I was in and I saw him and he gave me this scowl.
And I was like, oh, Lord, he's going to ask me why I'm here.
My French is so bad.
I'm like, oh, my God.
And he comes to me and he has this scowl still and he's talking to me in French.
And I'm like, I don't really know.
And I was like, and I said in French, I'm sorry, my French is not great.
I don't understand.
He was like, oh, where are you from?
He was like, oh, he started speaking English.
He was like, oh, I'm from Canada.
I had gotten so accustomed in America to people challenging my existence in a physical place that I didn't realize that I had that trauma.
I didn't know that I had been rejected so much in spaces that being accepted and just seen was refreshing.